# MIN WOO PARK PH.D. STUDENT

(+82) 010-4422-2943 alsdn0110@snu.ac.kr ↑ Home inLinkedin OGithub

**RESEARCH INTEREST** My research focuses on Causal Decision Making and Causal Effect Identification. I study how to graphically model a wide range of real-world problems in a causal manner and make optimal decisions. In particular, my research explores methods for making robust decisions, even when modeling with incomplete information, and decision-making processes in sequential settings.

## **EDUCATION**

### Graduate School of Data Science, Seoul National University

Seoul

M.S and Ph.D integrated course in Data Science

2022 - present

- Advisor: Prof. Sanghack Lee
- Research area: Causal Decision Making, Causal Effect Identification
- GPA: 4.17/4.3

### Department of Mathematics and Statistics, Sejong University

Seoul

B.S. in Applied Statistic and B.S. in Mathematics (Double Major)

2016 - 2022

- Advisor: Prof. Jieun Lee
- Research area: Operator Theory
- Overall GPA: 4.04/4.5 (Cum Laude)
- Major GPA: 4.46 & 4.38 / 4.5

# Work Experience

#### Graduate School of Data Science, Seoul National University

Causality Lab

Jan 2023 - present

Department of Mathematics and Statistics, Sejong University

Functional Analysis Lab

Jul 2021 - Dec 2022

Korea Military Service

National Service Conscript

Aug 2016 - Nov 2018

## **PUBLICATIONS**

- Complete Graphical Criterion for Sequential Covariate Adjustment in Causal Inference Yonghan Jung<sup>†</sup>, Min Woo Park, and Sanghack Lee<sup>†</sup> Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2024.
- 2. Convergence of the iterated mean transforms of a 2 × 2 matrix Ji Eun Lee\*† and Min Woo Park\* preprint, 2024.
- 3. Computation of the iterated Aluthge, Duggal, and Mean transforms Min Woo Park\*, and Ji Eun Lee\*† Filomat, 2023.

## Awards and Honors

5th place Award   2023 Mr. SNU body building competition	May 2023
4th place Award   The 9th College of Natural Sciences Academic Conference	Nov 2021
First Place Academic Scholarship   Sejong University	Fall 2021
Third Place Award   The 8th College of Natural Sciences Academic Conference	Nov 2020
First Place Academic Scholarship   Sejong University	Fall 2020

 $<sup>\</sup>ast$  for joint first authorship and  $^\dagger$  for corresponding author

Teaching Assistants	Causal Inference for Data Science Hyundai NGV Data Boot-Campus Causal Inference for Data Science Machine Learning and Deep Learning for Data Science II Basic Mathematics for Artificial Intelligence	Fall 2024 July 2024 - Sep 2024 Spring 2024 Fall 2023 Spring 2022
Invited Talks	SNU GSDS Pizza Seminar   Complete Graphical Criterion for Sequential Covariate Adjustment in Causal Inference	Dec 2024
Reference	Sanghack Lee   Seoul National University Assistant professor	sanghack@snu.ac.kr
	Ji Eun Lee   Sejong University Associate Professor	jieunlee7@sejong.ac.kr

Last updated: Nov 22, 2024